NUR IZZATI HUSNA BINTI MUHD ZIN

Nationality: Malaysian Mobile : 014-3032532

NRIC: 930830-02-5356 E-mail: <u>izzatihusnamuhdzin@gmail.com</u>

Age: 24 **Gender**: Female

Marital Status : Single Address : No 6, Jalan Keruing,

Kampung Tradisi Lembah Keriang,

06010 Changlun, Kedah Darul Aman



SUMMARY

She is graduated from Bachelor of Business Administration (Hons) Finance in Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM). Throughout her study, she has been exposed to various subjects such as Personal Financing Planning, Financial Market and Institutions, Corporate Finance, Investment Analysis, Futures and Options and many more. Besides, she has done her internship for four months at Universiti Utara Malaysia under administration department. She is a hardworking, optimistic, proactive and determined in whatever she does. Furthermore, she is able to work effectively in a team and manage to accomplish projects or assignment given within the time frame. She is very organized, flexible and willing to learn new things.

EDUCATION

2015-2017	Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Kedah
	Bachelor of Business Administration (Hons) Finance, CGPA: 2.90
2011-2014	Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Kedah
	Diploma in Banking, CGPA: 3.05
2010	Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Changlun
	Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM), Grade: 1A 2A- 1B+ 2B 2D 1E
2008	Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Changlun
	Penilaian Menengah Rendah (PMR), Grade: 4A 4B
2005	Sekolah Rendah Kebangsaan Dato' Wan Kemara
	Ujian Pencapaian Sekolah Rendah (UPSR), Grade: 3A 2B

EXPERIENCE

December 2016 – January 2017 Universiti Utara Malaysia Academic Affairs Department

- Assistant Invigilators
 - Distribute and collect the examination papers
 - Taking the students' attendance and supervise the students during examination held
 - Make a report to the invigilators if any academic cheating happen during the examination held

August 2016 – November 2016

Universiti Utara Malaysia

Student Development & Alumni Office College of Business

- Internship student
 - Managed to key in details of graduate employability survey among practicum College of Business students
 - Managed to create design poster for SDA COB event
 - Prepared paper works and online news for SDA COB events
 - Sorting and filing correspondent documents

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

- Personal Financial Planning
- Financial Market and Institution
- Corporate Finance
- Quantitative Business Analysis
- Monetary Economics

- Investment Analysis
- Islamic Finance
- Futures and Options
- Financial Statement Analysis
- Portfolio Management and Applications

SKILLS

Language

Malay

- Speaking
- Writing

English

- Speaking
- Writing

* * * * * *

Computer Software

Microsoft Office Tools

- Microsoft Words
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft PowerPoint

- * *
- **☆ ☆ ☆**

EXTRA CURRICULUR ACTIVITIES

Universiti Teknologi MARA, Kedah (2015-2017)

- Bachelor in Business Administration (Hons.) Finance
 - Committee in managing dinner of Faculty Business of UiTM Kedah
 - Participated in Program "Bengkel Microsoft Office Excel"
 - Committee in managing Program "Bengkel Microsoft Office Excel"
 - Badminton player for Bachelors Sports Festival of UiTM Kedah
 - Participated in "Persidangan Makro Kredit Islam 2016/1437H"
 - Participated in Color Run 2.0 of UiTM Kedah

- Participated in Investsmart's Unit Trust Seminar
- Participated in "Mini Program Latihan Keusahawanan Mahasiswa (PLKM)
- Participated in Program "Kem Kecemerlangan Akademik"

Universiti Teknologi MARA, Kedah (2011-2014)

- Diploma in Banking
 - Committee in managing an academic trip to "Jeruk Madu Pak Ali" in Penang

Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Changlun (2006-2010)

- Vice President (Kadet Remaja Sekolah)
- Vice President (Science Club)
- Class Assistant (2010)
- Participated in "Seminar on the Malaysian Communications & Multimedia Content Code and Internet Safety"
- Participated in Project Work "Additional Mathematics"
- Participated in "Xplorasi Lagenda Mahsuri"
- Participated in Program "Qiyamullail dan Kursus Kepimpinan Pengawas"

Sekolah Rendah Kebangsaan Dato' Wan Kemara (2000-2005)

- Secretary (Tunas Puteri)
- Committee member (Dam, Catur dan Karom)
- Librarian
- Participated in Program "Sukan Ria Kepanduan 2005"
- Participated in Program "Kursus Kepimpinan 2003"

ADDITIONAL INFO

- Language: Malay, English
- Malaysia University English Test (MUET): Band 2
- Willing to travel: Yes
- Interest: Playing badminton, Exercise and Music

REFERENCES

Puan Yaasmin Farzana Binti Abdul Karim Puan Syukriah Binti Ali

Industrial Training Coordinator

BBA (Hons) Finance

UiTM Cawangan Kedah

Email: yaasmin@kedah.uitm.edu.my

04-4562490 / 012-4103004

Lecturer of UiTM Kedah,

P.O.Box 187.

08400 Merbok, Kedah.

Email: syukriah@kedah.uitm.edu.mv

04-4562559